到目前为止的闪耀色彩
My name is Amana Osaki, and I'm 17 years old.
大崎あまな 17歳です
If I'm chosen as the cover
girl for your magazine,
もし 恩師のカバーガールに決まったら
I want to share its appeal with
as many people as possible!
恩師の魅力を たくさんの人に届けたいと思います
Amana-chan... You're accepted!
天菜ちゃん 合格
Huh? Already?!
えっ?もう?
Y-Yeah! Perfect!
う うん 完璧
No way! I want you to be tougher on me!
嘘だ もっと厳しくお願いしたいの
Oh, is that so... Well then...
そ そっか じゃあ
It's empty. I don't feel
anything from you at all!
空っぽですね 何も感じません
Chiyuki-san?
ちひゆきさん?
It's just a little game of
opposites, Tenka-chan.
反対ごっこよ 天下ちゃん
Opposites... game?
反対 ごっこ?
If you think of it as saying the
opposite of what you really feel,
思ってるのと反対のことを言う遊びだと思えば
even harsh words can be easier to handle!
きついことだって
Uh, your greetings... are kinda weak!
挨拶のキレが イマイチです
Besides, Osaki-san, you're busy
with Alstroemeria too, right?
それに 大崎さんはアルストロメリアとしてもお忙しいですよね
You can't fool me.
ごまかせませんよ
Can you really give us your all
while preparing for the album and tour?
アルバムやツアーの準備をしながら うちのために頑張れるんですか?
I'll do my best! I'll see
everything through to the end!
頑張ります 全部しっかりやり遂げます!
Y-You're accepted!
ご 合格!
Huh?! Wait, was that part
of the opposites game?
うえっ って反対ごっこ?
That... was a for-reals game!
今のは 本当ごっこ です
Geez, you're spoiling me too much!
もう あまなを甘やかしすぎ
But I understand.
You want to be well-prepared.
でもちゃんと準備したいのは分かるな
We also need to research that magazine
and come up with a plan, right?
その雑誌のこともリサーチして 対策しなきゃね
Yeah! It's a new magazine, I think it's
called something like "Apricot"...
うん 新しい雑誌らしいんだけど アプリコットみたいな名前で
What?
えっ
Huh? Wait... maybe it's not new,
it could be a reissue.
あれ 新しいんじゃなくて 復刊だったかも
Chiyuki-san?
ちゆきさん?
Ah, n-no, it's nothing!
あっ ううん
I used to read it thoroughly...
the special feature in Apricot.
よく読んだなあ アプリコットの特集
I just love it.
大好き
Thank you for helping us out so much.
ありがとう こんなに手伝ってくれて
It takes all three of us to
make Alstroemeria, right?
3人でアルストロメリアでしょ?
Yeah, let's aim for the Grand Prix!
うん 目指せ グランプリ
Yeah! I'll work hard, thinking
of us all being there together!
うん アマナ みんなで出ると思って頑張るね
If it's Amana-chan...
I'm certain it'll be wonderful.
アマナちゃんなら 素敵だよね
How nice...
いいな
Wow, Na-chan, you're amazing! So good!
すごい なあちゃん すごい上手
Practicing your walking?
ウォーキングの練習?
Ah, Chiyuki-san! Yeah!
あ 千雪さん うん
I'm supposed to learn from an instructor,
but I have to practice on my own, too.
専門の先生にも習うんだけど 自分でもやっとかなきゃって
But, you know, it's really hard to
get a booking with the instructor...
でもね 先生の予約がなかなか取れないんだ
I think I can get one the day after tomorrow,
but we don't have a place to practice.
明後日は撮れそうなんだけど 場所がなくて…
The day after tomorrow... Oh, because I
already reserved this place.
明後日…私がここを予約しちゃってるから
Ah, no, that's not what I meant!
あっ ううん そういうことじゃないんだ
B-but...
で でも
I'm sorry.
ごめんね
No, no, I'm the one who
said something weird...
ううん 天菜こそ変なこと言っちゃった
Oh, right, here!
あっ そうだ これ
I thought it might be helpful
for your studies, if you'd like.
あのね よかったらお勉強用にって思って
Wow, is this Apricot?
Chiyuki-san, you had this on hand?
あっ これアプリコット ちゆきさん持ってたの
No, I just found it at a
used bookstore yesterday.
ううん たまたま 昨日 古本屋さんで見つけて
It's so cute!
かわいい
Yeah, it's such... such
a wonderful magazine...
うん
Yeah, it's such... such
a wonderful magazine...
すっごく すっごくすてきな雑誌なの
Chiyuki-san...
ちゆきさん
Thank you, Chiyuki-san.
I'll study really hard!
ありがとう ちゆきさん あまなめっちゃ勉強するから
Um-hum.
うん
The three of us are Alstroemeria...
3人で アルストロメリア
It's just my own practice session...
私 ただの自主練なのに
Hey...
ねぇ
うん
You know, Chiyuki-san... do you
think she might really like Apricot?
あのね 千雪さんって もしかして アプリコット
I thought so too. It seems like...
she really likes it a lot...
てんかも 思った
I thought so too. It seems like...
she really likes it a lot...
とっても好きだったりするのかもって
I wonder why... me...
何でだろう 私
Why did it have to be Apricot?
何で アプリコットなんだろう
This is the last one...
しょ
これで 最後
Good wor—
お疲れさ
Could we possibly
reschedule the meeting again?
もう一度 お打ち合わせの時間をいただけませんか
No, but the idea that the Grand Prix has
already been decided in favor of Osaki is...
いや ですが グランプリが大崎に内定してるっていうのは
It's an honor, but...
とても光栄なことではあるんですが
When the three of us are together,
our voices are unbeatable!
3人揃ったら 最強の声だね
Yeah!
うん
Ahh!
ああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああああ
Wh-what's wrong?!
补
M-my stomach growled!
お お腹になっちゃった
Na-chan... are you hungry?
なあちゃん お腹空いてるの?
Here, take this.
じゃあ これ
Wow, really?!
あっ いいの
Of course. Right now, you need
all the energy you can get.
うん あまなちゃん 今は運とエネルギー使わないといけないんだもん
You should do your best for the audition.
オーディション頑張らなきゃね
Yeah, thank you... I'll do my best!
うん ありがとう 頑張るね
Oh, speaking of caramel, that reminds me—
あっ キャラメルで思い出したんだけど
there's this super cute flavored
latte that just came out!
めっちゃかわいいフレーバーラテが出てたの
Oh, r-really?
そ そうなの
Yeah! I'll get one for you tomorrow!
うん 明日買ってくるね
Thank you, that sounds really wonderful...
ありがとう それはすっごく素敵
but... um, remember to make
good use of your time...
だけど あの 時間を大事にして
and take care of yourself too, okay?
自分のことも考えなきゃ ね?
Y-you're right.
そ そうだよね
Ah, I'm sorry...
あ あの ごめんなさい
I didn't mean to sound preachy.
偉そうなこと
No, you're absolutely right!
ううん その通りだよ
I'm the one who should apologize...
アマナがごめんなさい
N-no, there's no need to apologize.
ううん ごめんだなんて
This is my fault...
アマナのせいだ
This is my fault.
私のせい
I'm overthinking it and
making things weird.
気にしすぎて変な感じにしちゃってる
Chiyuki-san is just trying to support me.
千雪さん アマナのこと応援してくれてるだけなのに
She probably realizes...
that I'm being strange...
きっと 分かっちゃってるよね
She probably realizes...
that I'm being strange...
私 変だもん
Na-chan... Chiyuki-san...
I... can't do anything...
なーちゃん 千ゆきさん
Na-chan... Chiyuki-san...
I... can't do anything...
てんか 何にも
The three of us, as Alstroemeria...
3人で アルストロメリア
ああああああああああああああああああああ
It's mom and the others.
ママ達だ
N-no.
あっ うううん
Sorry for showing up at
this hour unannounced.
ごめんなさい 遅くに突然
No, it's okay. What's going on?
ううん どうしたの
Um... I really wanted to
see you both and talk.
あの どうしても会ってお話したくて
So...
あのね
I want to try out for the
Apricot audition, too.
プリコットのオーディション 私も 受けたい
You probably guessed... Apricot is a
magazine I've always admired.
わかっちゃってるよね アプリコットは本当は私の すごく憧れの雑誌
That's why, as a devoted reader, my honest
wish is for Amana-chan to win, but....
だからアマナちゃんに勝ってほしいのは 愛読者としての本当の気持ち
That's why, as a devoted reader, my honest
wish is for Amana-chan to win, but....
でも
It's also true that I can't just
sit back and watch... I'm sorry.
見てるだけじゃいられないのも本当なの
It's also true that I can't just
sit back and watch... I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい
If I stay like this, I won't
be able to truly support you.
このままじゃ私 天菜ちゃんをちゃんと応援できない
So I realized I want to enter,
for my own sake.
だから 私は私のために出たいって思って
Please... Amana-chan.
お願いします 天菜ちゃん
Yes! Of course... absolutely!
うん そんなのもちろんだよ
I'll have to give it everything I've got!
アマナ 頑張らなくちゃ
I think it's jealousy...
Even I am surprised by it.
嫉妬…だと思うの 自分でも驚いちゃうけど
I know it is...
I just love that magazine, that's all...
分かってるの 私はただ好きってだけで
it's not like I could make
that world any more beautiful.
私があの世界を素敵にできるわけじゃない
If Amana-chan were the cover girl,
I'd still be absolutely thrilled.
天菜ちゃんがカバーガールだったら私 絶対ときめくもん
So, which one would you really prefer?
もうどっちなの?
It's truly both.
どっちもホントなの
So, in a way...
だから なんていうか
Auditioning is really
just to satisfy myself.
私がオーディションを受けるのは ただの自己満足
But that's not the only reason, is it?
だけでもないんじゃない?
If jealousy is going to create issues,
嫉妬のせいで迷惑かけちゃうくらいなら
wouldn't it be better to show
your support by competing openly?
堂々と戦うことで応援したい
Right?
でしょ?
Give it your best, Alstroemeria!
頑張れ
アルストロメリア
You know, I don't have much confidence...
アマナね 全然自信なくて
When I said, "I'll do my best," the
truth is... it's kind of the opposite.
頑張らなくちゃって言ったのは本当は 反対
Maybe it's the same for both of us, but...
二人ともかもだけど
there's a chance only one
of us will be chosen, right?
どっちかだけ選ばれないことだってあるよね
If that happens, we might not be
able to be like we were before...
そうなったら 今までみたいに
If...
もし
If you're really worried...
then you don't have to enter!
もし心配だったら
If you're really worried...
then you don't have to enter!
で でなくていいよ
But... if you do enter,
you have to give it your all.
で 出るなら全力 出さなきゃ
Yeah, and I think Chiyuki-san
will too... for sure...
うん
Yeah, and I think Chiyuki-san
will too... for sure...
千雪さんもきっと…
But, because
でも だから
we're both giving it our best...
全力だから
I'm scared of what will happen
if one of us loses.
負けた時が怖いよ
Producer!
プロデューサーさん
I'm sorry! I...
ごめんなさい あまな
I'm withdrawing from the audition!
オーディションを辞退します
Amana-chan!
あまなちゃん
I gave it a lot of thought.
アマナね いっぱい考えたの
I want to support Chiyuki-san!
She's the one who truly suits Apricot!
アマナ チユキさんを応援したい
I want to support Chiyuki-san!
She's the one who truly suits Apricot!
アプリコットにぴったりなの チユキさんなんだもん
I know that, and yet...
I don't even know how to
give it my best anymore...
それが分かってるのに どうやって頑張ったらいいのか分からないよ
Amana, could you hear me out—?
アマナ、聞いてくれるか
I'm so sorry! I know doing something
like this is causing a lot of trouble...
ごめんなさい すっごく すっごく迷惑かかっちゃうよね こんなこと
But going into the audition with
these feelings isn't right either!
でも こんな風に思いながら出場するの もっと良くないよ
Amana...
アマナ
I'll withdraw from the audition.
私がエントリーを取りやめます
Ch-Chiyuki-san...
ち ちえきさん
This is my fault. I... didn't
understand anything.
私のせいです 私 何にも分かってなかった
I had convinced myself that Amana-chan
would win the Grand Prix...
あまなちゃんがグランプリになるってどこかで信じ込んでて
I thought I understood what it meant to
truly compete and how Amana-chan felt,
本当に勝負するっていうことも 天菜ちゃんのことも
but I really didn't.
分かってるつもりで全然
I understand how both of you feel.
二人の気持ちは分かった
But I called you here today because
there's something I need to tell you.
でもな 今日呼んだのは伝えなきゃいけないことがあるからなんだ
The truth is, for this audition...
このオーディション
Amana has already been selected
as the Grand Prix winner.
天野のグランプリが内定した
I thought your decision to enter the
audition was admirable, Chiyuki.
オーディションに出るって決断 俺はすごいと思った
But... the Grand Prix won't be yours.
でも グランプリは千雪じゃない
I want you to think about whether there's
still a reason for you to compete.
それでも出場する理由があるのか 考えてほしい
I'm not fond of handling
things this way, either.
俺もこういうやり方は好きじゃないよ
But the client made this decision after
evaluating Amana's past activities.
でも 先方がアマナのこれまでの活動を評価して 決めたことなんだ
I'll respect Amana's choice
about whether or not to withdraw.
辞退するかは アマナの意見を尊重する
No matter what decision you make,
I'll support you both fully.
どんな結論を出したとしても 全力でサポートする
So...
だから
I want you to think hard about
what's truly most important to you.
何が自分にとって 一番大事なのか
I want you to think hard about
what's truly most important to you.
もう一回考えてみてほしい
For me...
私にとって
The most... important thing...
一番 大事なこと
How about we walk a little
more before heading back?
もうちょっと歩いてから帰らない?
Yeah...
うん
When the three of us are together,
our voices are unbeatable!
3人そろったら 最強の声だね
My voice... no, I can't hear it...
it's like it won't come out.
声…
My voice... no, I can't hear it...
it's like it won't come out.
ううん 聞こえないよ
My voice... no, I can't hear it...
it's like it won't come out.
出てないみたい
She's the one who truly suits Apricot!
アプリコットにぴったりなの 千雪さんなんだもん
あー
あーー
Chiyuki-san?
ちゆきさん?
I used to practice vocal
exercises here a lot.
あたし 前はよくここで発声練習してて
补
It seems like my voice still
isn't coming out properly...
まだ喉が開いてないみたい
M-Me too...
て てんかも
补
Ch-Chiyuki-san! Um...
ち 千雪さん あの
I... I...
あ あの
Yes...
うん
S-sorry, it looks like I'm
losing my voice too...
ご ごめん あまなもちょっと出ないみたい 声
Amana-chan...
天ちゃん
Hey...
ねえ
How about we play the
"Game of Opposites" again?
反対ごっこ しよっか
Amana-chan! I hope you fail the audition!
あまなちゃん オーディション落ちたらいいのにー
Let your voice out! All right,
Amana-chan, it's your turn!
っ出していいの声
Let your voice out! All right,
Amana-chan, it's your turn!
はい アマナちゃんの番
I hope both of you fail the audition!
二人とも オーディション落ちたらいいのに
Na-chan! It's okay if you lose!
なーちゃん 負けてもいいよ
If you lose, it'll... destroy
what's most important!
負ければ こわれちゃうから 大事なもの!
Chiyuki-san! I hope you fail the audition!
ちゆきさん オーディション 落ちればいいのにー
I really, really, really hope you fail!
ちゆきさんが 絶対 絶対絶対 落ちればいいのに
Both of you... fail!
2人とも 落ちて!
I want to lose!
負けた——い!
I want to lose, too!
天野も 負けた——い
Both of you... lose!
2人とも 負けて——
And... I absolutely hate Alstroemeria!
もう アルストロメリアなんか
大っきらい
Alstroemeria is... not what's most important!
アルストロメリア なんか
一番 大事じゃ ない
Alstroemeria is... Alstroemeria is...
アルストロメリアなんか
アルストロメリア なんか
... is something I hate, and
it's not what's most important.
大っきらいだし 一番大事じゃない
Chiyuki-san...
ちゆきさん
The "Game of Opposites" is over.
反対ごっこ 終わり
字幕制作：北宇治字幕组Deep State
翻译：FFU2
后期：Scrpr
分かっていて欲しいなんて
一方的すぎるオビニオン
素直になれたらいいのに
単純なことを邪魔するプライド
大事にしたいと思ったり
喜ばせてあげたいと思ったり
特別だって気づいたら
言葉にしてあげなくちゃ
You're the one　あなたは私の太陽
You're only one　私はあなたの太陽
どんなときも優しく照らし合おうよ
届けるためのプリリィクエル
これから始まる未来のすべてが
楽しいことばかりじゃないとしても
手をつないだら歩き出そう
ずっとだよ　with you　この愛を信じてる
Alstromeria是…